National Organization for Women, New York State Chapter; Records apap029
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1965-2011; 2; 22.17 cubic ft.
  - Lobby Groups, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Lobbying Contacts- Albany, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Lobbying Day Notes- February 26, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Lobbying and Legislation (1 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Lobbying and Legislation (2 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Lobbying Services, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Lobbyist Reports, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Lobbyist Resumes (1 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Lobbyist Resumes (2 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Long Island Black American Day Committee Inc., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Long Island Chapter- Nassau, 1978-1982; 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Long Island Convention, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Long Island- PAC, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Long Island Women's Coalition, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - The Long Term Impact of Divorce on Children: A Fist Report from a 25-Year Study, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Looking Forward- Looking Back, Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Lori Gardner- Candidate- Executive V.P., Undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Los Angeles NOW Bld., 1997 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Luncheon with Sonia Johnson- June 24, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - The Magic of Membership, Undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Mail, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Mail - Incoming- Non-NOW Individuals, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Mail- Outgoing to National NOW, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Mailing- Chapter Presidents, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Mailing- Outgoing- Non-NOW Individuals, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Maine NOW Bill of Conscience - Thinking About the Future, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Major Recent Media Success, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Majority Caucus, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Making Sense of the Utterly Senseless- Montreal Murders, Undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Making Waves- Awards Ceremony, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - March For Peace, 2007; Undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - March for Women's Equality and Women's Lives, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - March for Women's Lives- Organizing Tips, Undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - March to Fight the Right, 1996; Undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Marcia Pappas- Certificate of Appreciation, Undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Marcia Pappas- Devoted Leader for Today, Undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Marcia Pappas- Discussing the Time is NOW - Grass Roots Organizing for Social Change for Civil Rights, Undated
  - Marcia Pappas- Headshots, Undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Marcia Pappas- Next Action V.P., Undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Marcia Pappas- Presidential Campaign, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Marcia Pappas- Resignation Letter, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Marcia Pappas- Resume, 2009; Undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Marcia Pappas- Speeches, 1992-1993; 1996; 1998; 2003-2005; Undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Marcia Pappas- Thank You for Sexual Assault Legislation, Undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Marcia Pappas- Veterans of Foreign Wars Awards, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Margaret Dodd- Resume, Undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Marilyn Fitterman- Letters of Recommendation, 1999; 2003; Undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Mario Cuomo, News- Press Statements, 1992; 1994; Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Marriage and Divorce Task Force, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Marta Rollova, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Materials Catalog, Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Maternity Health Act, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Matrimonial Actions, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Matrimonial Information, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Matrimonial Legislation, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Media Contact List, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Media Credential Request Forms, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Media List, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Media Packet I, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Media Packet II, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Media Reform, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Media Reports, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Mediation Course, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Medicaid Reimbursement, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Meeting Change, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Meeting Notice for Northeast Regional Board Meetings, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Meeting Photos, Undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Member Concerns, 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Member - Leadership Information (1 of 4), 1984-1988 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Member - Leadership Information (2 of 4), 1984-1988 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Member - Leadership Information (3 of 4), 1984-1988 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Member - Leadership Information (4 of 4), 1984-1988 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Membership, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Membership 101, 1989; 1999; Undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Membership Processing Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Memorandums- General Announcements, 1972-1974; Undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Memos (1 of 3), 1981-1982; 1988; 1998-2002; 2008-2009; Undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Memos (2 of 3), 1981-1982; 1988; 1998-2002; 2008-2009; Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Memos (3 of 3), 1981-1982; 1988; 1998-2002; 2008-2009; Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Memphis Guide, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Middletown, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Mid-Hudson Chapter, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Mid-Hudson NOW Membership Form, 1989; Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Mid-Life Older Women's Health, 1987-1992 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Mid-Suffolk Chapter Information, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Midwives, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Millennium Summit: To Your Health, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Minutes Foundation Updates, 1998; 2000 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Missouri NOW, Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Mobilization for Women's Lives, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Model Statutory Provisions For States Adopting the Family Violence Option, Undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Molly Yard- Missouri NOW State Conference, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Molly Yard- Syracuse Everson Museum, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Moms At The Office, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Monroe-Woodbury Bus Drivers, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Mothers Matter, Caregivers Count, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Mohawk Valley Chapter, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Moving Forwards Together- Strategy Summit and Celebration, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Muriel Fox- NOW- New York State Women to Women Award, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Mutual Orders of Protection Project, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - My Voice/ My Choice- NOW Oral History of Reproductive Rights, Unddated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Mylan Denerstein- Work With Attorney General Cuomo, Undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Names for NOW Foundation, Undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Nassau NOW- 20th Anniversary, 1982; 1989 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - National Advertisers and Rush Limbaugh Shows, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - National Advisory Council on Women's Educational Programs (NACWEP), 1980 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - National Board, 1971-1972; 1977; 1980-1981; 1996 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - National Board Meetings (1 of 2), 1987; 1989-1992; 1995-1998; 1999; 2000-2006 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - National Board Meetings (2 of 2), 1987; 1989-1992; 1995-1998; 1999; 2000-2006 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - National Board Member Job Description, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - The National Coalition For Immigrant Women's Rights, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - National Coalition of American Nuns, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - National Committee to Work on Family Law Issues, Undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - National Event of World March of Women in 2000 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - National Institute of Education- Curriculum Development, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - National Lesbian Rights Conference Lesbian Rights Agenda- October 16, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - National Mall, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - National March for Housing NOW, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - National March for Women's Lives, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - National NOW Documents, 2002-2003; Undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - National NOW Family Advisory Committee, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - National NOW Conference, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - National NOW Information, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - National Office, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - National Women's Day, 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - New Activist Training Institute, 2006-2007 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - New Hampshire NOW, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - New Jersey NOW, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - New Members for NOW- New Member Recruitment and Retention for Chapters, 1994; 1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - New Phone Number East End Chapter, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - New York Chapter Association of Family and Conciliation Courts - A Panel Dialogue on Proposed Maintenance Guidelines, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - New York City Chapter, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - New York City Commission on the Status of Women - Election Victories, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - New York Court Structure, Judicial Reform and Access to Justice, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - New York Public Interest and Research Group, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - "New York" Renewal Monetary Report, 1999; 2003 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - New York State Assembly - Annual Report - Task Force on Women's Issues, Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - New York State Assembly Citation-Recognition of Marica Pappas, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - New York Sate BAR Association - Report on the Task Force on the Family Law, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - New York State Coalition for Post - Martial Compensation Guidelines, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - New York State Court Structure, Judicial Reform, and Access to Justice, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - New York State Division for Women, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - New York State- NARAL Headcounts, 1991; Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - New York State and National NOW Membership Surveys, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - New York State Nurses Associations, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - New York State and Pennsylvania 13 Laws, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - New York Temporary Commission on Lobbying, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - New York Women's Sports Association, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Newburgh-Orange County Feminist Union, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - No-Fault Divorce Legislation Meeting, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - No-Fault Divorce- Speech, Undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - No Myths- No Distortions- Only Stark Reality, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Nominations Committee, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Noreen R. Connell- President of NOW- New York State Papers, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Northeast Region Bylaws, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Northeast Region Women of Color and Allies Summit, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Northeast Regional Young Feminist Summit, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Northern Chautauqua, 1974; 1986 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Not For Ourselves Alone- A Leadership Skills Conference, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Notes for Talk at Activist Training Session, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Notices, 1977-1979; Undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - NOW Account Summary, 2001; 2005 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - NOW Action Center Contact List, 2005; Undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - NOW Action Center - Email Instructions, Undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - NOW Action Center Staff, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - NOW Acts!, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - NOW Alliance PAC- Long Island Annual Fundraisers, 1987-1990 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - NOW Alliance PAC- Long Island Meeting Agendas, 1987-1994 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - NOW Alliance PAC of Long Island - Officers and Delegates, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - NOW Campus Actions Network, Undated (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - NOW- CAN- Campus Action Network, Undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - NOW- Candidates, Undated (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - NOW Cash Flow, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - NOW Chapters in Central Dues Collection States, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - NOW Chapters without EIN Numbers, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - NOW Conference Resolutions- Memphis, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - NOW Declaration of Sentiments, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - NOW Denounces No-Fault Divorce Legislation, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - NOW Direct Marketing Report, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - NOW and Domestic Relations, Undated (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - NOW Donor Policy, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - NOW Equality Report, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - NOW Expense Voucher Instructions, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Now Feminism, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - NOW Foundation Board Meeting, 1997; 1999; 2006 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - NOW Foundation Inc., Undated (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - NOW Foundation Public Policy Report, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - NOW Foundation's Young Feminist Skills Building Summit, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - NOW Guidelines for Feminist Consciousness-Raising, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - NOW in the News (1 of 4), 1989-2000; Undated (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - NOW in the News (2 of 4), 1989-2000; Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - NOW in the News (3 of 4), 1989-2000; Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - NOW in the News (4 of 4), 1989-2000; Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Now in the News- Press Clips (1 of 2), 1998-1999; Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - NOW in the News- Press Clips (2 of 2), 1998-1999; Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - NOW in the News: Press Clips Addendum, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - NOW in the News: Press Releases (1 of 4), 1976-2010; Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - NOW in the News: Press Releases (2 of 4), 1976-2010; Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - NOW in the News: Press Releases (3 of 4), 1976-2010; Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - NOW in the News: Press Releases (4 of 4), 1976-2010; Undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - NOW Inc. and Now Foundation National Board Meeting, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - NOW- Introduction, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - NOW LDEF Membership Meeting, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1994; 1998-2000; Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund- Financial Statements, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund- Legal Docket, 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund- Statement, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - NOW Litigation Report, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - NOW Lobbying Tips, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - NOW- Marketing Proposal, Undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - NOW- Membership by State, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - NOW- "A Million Voices For Economics Justice"- Campaign, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - NOW National Board, 1987-1992 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - NOW National Board/ Coordinators/ Presidents, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - NOW National Board Meeting Minutes, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - NOW National Board Report, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - NOW National Board's Ongoing Commitment to Fundraising, Undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - NOW- National Conference Procedure Guides (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - NOW- National Conference Resolution, 2004; 2006 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - NOW National Conferences, 1987; 1991-1994; 1996-1998; 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - NOW National Conferences, 1987; 1991-1994; 1996-1998; 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - NOW- National Convention- Passed Resolutions, 1989; Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - NOW- National Nevada, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - NOW National Order Forms, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - NOW- New Jersey, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - NOW- New York City Chapter, 1984-1985; 1987 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - NOW- New York City - Songs Chants, Undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - NOW- New York City- Women's Suffrage Event, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - NOW- New York State- 2002 Candidate Declarations (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - NOW New York State Call For Choice, Undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - NOW- New York State Chapter Addresses, Undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - NOW- New York State Chapter President and Council Delegates, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - NOW- New York State Conference, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - NOW- New York State Convention Minutes, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - NOW- New York State Convention- Plenary Session, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - NOW- New York State Conventions, 1987; 2005 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - NOW- New York State Council Meeting, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - NOW- New York State Council Minutes, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - NOW- New York State Diversity Plan, Undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - NOW- New York State Election Candidate Platforms, 1988; 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - NOW- New York State Executive Committee Lists - RESTRICTED, 1993-1998; 2002-2003; Undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - NOW- New York State Financial Records (2 of 2), 1975; 1986-1988; 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - NOW- New York State Financial Records (1 of 2), 1975; 1986-1988; 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - NOW- New York State Foundation- An Evening of Entertainment Reception Reservation, Undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - NOW- New York State Foundation Meeting, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - NOW- New York State Foundation Meetings, 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - NOW- New York State - Gotham Chapter, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - NOW- New York State Inc. Convention- Letter From Hillary Clinton, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - NOW- New York State Information, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Now- New York State International Feminist Study Tour- Mexico, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - NOW- New York State Leaders, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - NOW- New York State Lobbyist- Contract for Employment, Undated (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - NOW- New York State Media Packet, 1997; 1998 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - NOW- New York State- National Central Dues Projection, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - NOW- New York State- Plenary Session, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - NOW- New York State Politics, 2001-2002; Undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - NOW New York State - Special Leadership Awards (Legislative Resolution), 1986 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - NOW- New York State Task Force Plan on Women of Color Rights, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - NOW- New York State Treasury Report, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - NOW- New York State Women's Health and Privacy Protection Petition, Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - NOW- Northeast Regional Conference, 1989-1990; 1996 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - NOW- Northeast Regional Conference, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - NOW and NOW Foundation Action Center Staff, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - NOW PAC Endorsed Candidates- Working Document, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - NOW Political Endorsements, Undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - NOW Power Team, Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - NOW- Process Committee, 1989; 1992 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - NOW Profit and Loss Budget v. Actual, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - NOW Reports on Equal Rights Amendment, Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - NOW Reports on Twenty Years of Feminism, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - NOW Resources in Spanish, Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - NOW Staff, 1996-1998 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - NOW Statement of Purpose, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - NOW Statement of Purpose, Undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - NOW Survey of Chapters, 1989-1998 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - NOW Tax Return, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - NOW v. Randall Terry, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - NOW v. Scheidler (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - NOW v. Scheidler (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - NOW Vision For New York, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - NOW's History, Undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - NOW's Message, Undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Office Space Business, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Officers- Greater Rochester NOW, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Official PAC Manual, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Official PAC Manual, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Olympic Park and Otherside Night Club Bombing, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - On History, Womanhood, and Liberalism: In the Shadow of the Republican Convention - Keynote Blanche Wiesin Cook, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Oneonta- Delaware Country, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Open Letter to the Assembly, Undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Open Letter to Governor Mario Cuomo, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Operating Rules and Procedures for New York State NOW Political Action Committee, Undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Operation Goliath, Undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Operation Rescue- Opinion, 1989; 1991 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Operation Rescue Statewide Survey, Undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Orange County- NOW, 1989; Undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Order Forms- 1993 Citizens' Guide to the New York State Legislature, Undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Organization of Women Legal Awareness, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Organization Review, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Organizational Guide and Information, 1970-1974 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Organize to Win- A Grassroots Activist Handbook: A Guide to Help People Organize Community Campaigns, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Orleans County, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Ortho- 21st Century Women Awards, Undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Out of the Shadows- Strategies for Expanding State Labor and Civil Rights Protections for Domestic Workers, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - PAC (1 of 2), 1980-1986; 1992; 1994 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - PAC (2 of 2), 1980-1986; 1992; 1994 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - PAC Budget, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - PAC Endorsements, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - The PAC Handbook, Undated (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - PAC Meeting, 1996-1998 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - PAC Questionnaire Responses (1 of 4), 1992; 1994; 1997-2000; 2002; Undated (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - PAC Questionnaire Responses (2 of 4), 1992; 1994; 1997-2000; 2002; Undated (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - PAC Questionnaire Responses (3 of 4), 1992; 1994; 1997-2000; 2002; Undated (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - PAC Questionnaire Responses (4 of 4), 1992; 1994; 1997-2000; 2002; Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - PAC Report, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - PAC Request for Endorsement or Support, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - PAC- State Coordinators, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Packets, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Packets and Issues, 1977-1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Paid Family Leave- Marcia Pappas Public Hearing, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Paid Vouchers, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission: Reform Proposal, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Pamela K. Martens, Judith P. Mione v. Smith Barney, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Parental Consent on Abortions for Minors, 1987; 1990; Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Parental Leave, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Park Project Inc. (Hiring Practices of Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Passing the Torch of Feminism, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Patricia Ireland- "We Won't Go Back", 1992 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Patropoly- Monroe County/ New York State? USA Game for the "Welfare" of Unscrupulous Spouses, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Pay Equality - New York City, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Pay Equality Rally, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Pay Equality- State, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - P/C Caucus Meeting, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - PEACE Program, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Pennsylvania NOW, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - People v. Garson- Transcript of Robing Room Video, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Personnel Policy Manual, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Personnel Policy of Illinois NOW, Undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Petition for Women's Lives, Undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Phil Schilliro - Congress Endorsement, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Philanthropic Support of the Women's Movement, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Phelps Dodge- Arizona Copper Strike, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Phone Tree, Undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Pigeon and Lafalce Poll, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Plattsburgh, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 32)